export const questions = [
  {
    question: 'How many kids does Jalal have?',
    answers: ['0', '1', '2 (that we know of)', 'He went Genghis Khan mode'],
    correctIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following actors did not appear in the groundbreaking film "Morbius" (2022)?',
    answers: ['Jared Harris', 'Samuel L. Jackson', 'Jared Leto', 'Matt Smith'],
    correctIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: 'In the video game Among Us, which is not one of the rooms on the spaceship?',
    answers: ['Trash Compactor', 'Cafeteria', 'Electrical', 'O2'],
    correctIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is the goddess of agriculture?',
    answers: ['Artemis', 'Hera', 'Athena', 'Demeter'],
    correctIndex: 3,
  },
  {
    question: 'How many times does the average person blink a day?',
    answers: ['12,500 to 16,800', '14,400 to 19,200', '15,000 to 18,600', '16,200 to 20,700'],
    correctIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: 'What sport has been played on the moon?',
    answers: ['Golf', 'Basketball', 'Tennis', 'Gymnastics'],
    correctIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: 'How many teeth does an aardvark have?',
    answers: ['0', '8', '18', '26'],
    correctIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: 'What country consumes the most chocolate?',
    answers: ['Germany', 'England', 'Switzerland', 'Norway'],
    correctIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: 'What percentage of undergrad students at U of C are international?',
    answers: ['10%', '15%', '20%', '25%'],
    correctIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: 'In Georgia, USA, what food is illegal to eat with a fork?',
    answers: ['French fries', 'Fried chicken', 'Pizza', 'BBQ ribs'],
    correctIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: 'What country has won the most World Cups?',
    answers: ['Argentina', 'France', 'Germany', 'Brazil'],
    correctIndex: 3,
  },
  {
    question: 'If you dug a hole through the center of the Earth starting from Spain, where would you end up?',
    answers: ['Australia', 'Indonesia', 'New Zealand', 'Tonga'],
    correctIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: 'What sea creature kills the most humans per year?',
    answers: ['Killer whale', 'Blue ringed octopus', 'Great white shark', 'Box jellyfish'],
    correctIndex: 3,
  },
  {
    question: 'What unit is the movement of a computer mouse measured in?',
    answers: ['Mickeys', 'Sydharb', 'Microfortnight', 'Muggeseggele'],
    correctIndex: 0,
  },
];
